# WILLIAM A. LUCHT

IT/WEB DEVELOPER

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

E-Commerce, A/B Testing
Magento
Adobe Creative Suite
MySQL
PHP
HTML
CSS/SASS
Javasctipt/JQuery
React
OOP
Agile Methodologies
Git/Github
Jira/Confluence/Bitbucket

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Reliable and professional Organized Time management Team player Motivated High Level Problem Solving Skills

### CONTACT

+1 858 603 4860 aaronlucht@gmail.com LinkedIn

#### REFERENCES

#### **DUSTIN CHESSNUTT**

Web Developer dustinchessnutt@yahoo.com

#### **KEITH MEINERTS**

IT Manager - American Express +1 480 215 2522

# ANDREW HERNANDEZ

Architect - RAH Architecture +1 949 554 7124 andrewh@raharchitecture.con

#### MICHAEL REYNOSO

Project Manager - FedCon Group +1 619 993 8458 mikereynoso@fedcongroup.com

#### **PROFILE**

A highly motivated Web and IT specialist with over six years of experience assisting clients in the private sector launch and maintain their websites and infrastructure. Advanced knowledge of building efficient e-commerce solutions including Bigcommerce, Magento, Salesforce and Woocommerce. Detailed knowledge of managing and planning website builds and assisting clients in maximizing the utility of their online presence. Seeking a position to grow and expand into new and emerging Web/IT technologies.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### FEDERAL CONSTRUCTION SUPERINTENDENT

Federal Construction Group | Dec 2019 - Dec 2020

Worked with the Federal Government on Fire Alarm installation at the Point Loma submarine base. Worked alongside Project Managers to install, troubleshoot, and repair new fire Alarm Systems. Obtained Osha 30-Safety certification, 40-hour EM385 certification, and the USACE Construction Quality Management For Contractors certification.

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECT MANAGER

V-Digital Services/The Phoenix New Times | Aug 2018 - Oct 2019

Onboarded, prepared, managed, and launched web development projects nationwide. I worked rigorously with my web team to design, build and launch web projects that included small ecommerce stores to large corporate websites for name brands such as <a href="Four Peaks Brewing(Anheuser-Busch">Four Peaks Brewing(Anheuser-Busch)</a>) and <a href="Wine & Design">Wine & Design</a> (featured on ABC's <a href="Font Peaks Brank">Shark Tank</a>)

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Mt. Baker Vapor | Sept 2017 - April 2018

As the sole Web Developer for a multi-million dollar company, it was my role to maintain the company website and codebase, create new content pages via BigCommerce's stencil CLI file structure, assist other departments on backend website errors, build product pages, and assist in our Salesforce implementation. Was company point of contact for all internal IT questions in relation to company website operations.

## **EDUCATION**

# BACHELOR OF SCIENCE DEGREE: WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

Platt College San Diego | 2012 - 2016

#### **OSHA 30-HOUR SAFETY CERTIFICATION**

OSHA Online Training Course | 2020

#### **40-HOUR EM385 SAFETY CERTIFICATION**

USACE/NAVFAC Online Training Course | 2020

## CONSTRUCTION QUALITY MANAGEMENT FOR CONTRACTORS

USACE/NAVFAC Online Training Course | 2020